Ethan@Your room is very girly.
Emily@What are you talking about?
Ethan@Well... it smells nice.
Ethan@You're reading books too?
Emily@Yes, I am.
Ethan@I really like the author of this book.
Emily@I know.
Ethan@You know?
Ethan@What other books do you read?
Ethan@What's wrong?
Emily@Nothing.
Ethan@You keep a handwritten diary?
Ethan@Aren't many people forgetting how to write characters these days?
Emily@Yeah, that's true.
Ethan@Let me take a look.
Emily@No, not yet!
Emily@It's just my random scribblings.
Ethan@Is that so?
Ethan@How mysterious.
Emily@There's nothing special in it.
Ethan@Alright then.
Ethan@So, what are you going to do later?
Emily@Later... I don't have any plans.
Ethan@What's this?
@Ethan, do you know? You're the last person I think about before I sleep and the first thing I think of when I wake up. Thank you for always being there for me when I'm down. I've started to get used to having you around, so I want to ask you something!
Ethan@Actually, I also...
Ethan@No, wait.
Ethan@I, I, I wasn't sure before.
Ethan@Do, do you like me too?
Ethan@Anyway, thank you.
Ethan@Thank you for liking me too.
Ethan@I think it's about time.
Ethan@I, I should go now.
Ethan@Let's meet again next time.
Emily@Wait a moment.
Emily@Can you stay with me a little longer?
Emily@Is that okay?